Joseph Tolentino cayamanda

Junior Front-End developer

Ferrara, Emilia-Romagna, Emilia-Romagna 44124 jphctolentino@gmail.com - 327 568 6919

Am a passionate self-taught junior web developer that already did front-end works as freelancer and able to follow instructions from clients and fellow developers/designers and the period passed in the bakery taught me how to not think about the problem but, think about the solution with my colleagues; Following my roadmap into becoming a full-stack developer. Now tapping into the basics of React.js. I am 27 years old and currently living in Ferrara(FE), Italy.

Willing to relocate to: London

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

14spm.com - Italia

Contacted for a freelance work that consists in re-coding a previously coded website with Wix.com into a simpler html-css website.

Very first commercial work as a front-end developer.

Learned to use version/source controls.

Learned to interact with the clients.

Learned to follow detailed instructions.

Learned how to communicate with fellow developers and designers.

All Rounder

Local Bakery - Ferrara -

July 2015 to February 2017

started as a delivery guy then ended up as an all-rounder. From workspace preparation to production to post-production and delivery.

Learned to cooperate with my colleagues to find solutions for our problems even in most stressful days of work.

Delivery Driver

Private - Ferrara -

January 2012 to January 2013

Delivery guy for a private company which delivers dentists' supplies and products. Drived a lot.

EDUCATION

diploma in Architecture

Gian Battista Aleotti - Ferrara

June 2005 to July 2010

SKILLS

Ajax (Less than 1 year), css (Less than 1 year), html (Less than 1 year), JavaScript (Less than 1 year), Git (Less than 1 year), Jquery (Less than 1 year), Reactjs (Less than 1 year)

LINKS

https://josephtolentino.net